https://www.displaysandholders.com/privacy-policy

Displays and Holders
Search:
Search
Displays and Holders
Menu
Home
ProductsMost Popular DisplaysCOVID-19 PPEShields, Barriers and Sneeze GuardsCountertop Acrylic ShieldsOne Sided ShieldsNo Opening6" High Access Slot12" High Access SlotThree Sided ShieldsTwo Sided ShieldsVelcro Cashier ShieldsHanging Acrylic BarrierScrew Mount BarriersTable DividersFloor Standing ShieldsAcrylic Barrier AccessoriesHanging Mount AccessoriesTable Mount AccessoriesCubicle Wall AccessoriesFloor Standing AccessoriesPanel ConnectorsProtective Guards by IndustryGuards for OfficesGuards for SchoolsGuards for Nail SalonsAcrylic Care & CleaningPPE DispensersSafety Signs & DecalsVirtually Unbreakable DisplaysSign Holders & Table TentsAngled FramesSide Loading FramesTop Loading FramesTop Loading - Flat BaseBottom Loading FramesSingle Sided TentsDouble Sided Tents Bookstyle Table Tents Four Sided Table TentSix Sided Table TentsThree Sided Table TentEight Sided Table TentsPremium Sign HoldersAcrylic Picture FramesAcrylic Bases/GripsWall Mount Sign HoldersFold Over Wall FramesTop Loading Wall FramesWall Frames with NotchSide Loading Wall FramesSlatwall Sign HoldersStandoff Poster FramesPhoto Booth FramesShelf TalkersBrochure & Literature HoldersCounter Brochure HoldersSingle Pocket HoldersFits up to 4.25" wide Fits up to 6"wideFits up to 8.5"wideFits up to 11"wideMulti-Pocket HoldersEconomy CountertopDeluxe Series HoldersCombination Holders and FramesRotating HoldersJ-StandsWall Mounted HoldersSingle Pocket HoldersEconomy Wall MountFits up to 4.5"wide insertsFits up to 6"wide insertsFits up to 8.5"wide insertsFits up to 11"wide insertsFlat Foldable PocketsMulti-Pocket HoldersSlatwall Brochure HoldersMulti-Pocket HoldersCombination Frames & HoldersSuggestion & Ballot BoxesWithout Sign Header (Riser)With Sign Header (Riser)Open Top BinsWall Mount BoxesWall Poster/Certificate FramesFold Over Wall FramesTop Loading Wall FramesWall Poster Frame with NotchSide Loading Wall FramesSlatwall Sign HoldersBusiness Card DisplaysAccessories & Add-OnsAcrylic ComponentsAdd-On PocketsMounting AccessoriesCeiling HardwareWall HardwareTable HardwareGlass HardwareMagnetic HardwareBallot Box AccessoriesReal Estate & Outdoor
HoldersMerchandise DisplaysMemo Pad / Sticky Note HoldersJ-StandsOpen Top BinsU-RisersCD / DVD HoldersRetail Displays & FixturesEaselsSlatwall DisplaysSlatwall Bins & ShelvesSlatwall Brochure HoldersSlatwall Sign HoldersImprinting ServicesImprinting OptionsAcrylic Care | CleaningAcrylic Flat SheetsMedical IndustryOverstock/Clearance
My Cart
My Account
Buyer's Guide
Buyers Guide
Differences in Material
Thickness of Material
FAQ
Video
Brands
ProductsMost Popular DisplaysCOVID-19 PPEShields, Barriers and Sneeze GuardsCountertop Acrylic ShieldsOne Sided ShieldsNo Opening6" High Access Slot12" High Access SlotThree Sided ShieldsTwo Sided ShieldsVelcro Cashier ShieldsHanging Acrylic BarrierScrew Mount BarriersTable DividersFloor Standing ShieldsAcrylic Barrier AccessoriesHanging Mount AccessoriesTable Mount AccessoriesCubicle Wall AccessoriesFloor Standing AccessoriesPanel ConnectorsProtective Guards by IndustryGuards for OfficesGuards for SchoolsGuards for Nail SalonsAcrylic Care & CleaningPPE DispensersSafety Signs & DecalsVirtually Unbreakable DisplaysSign Holders & Table TentsAngled FramesSide Loading FramesTop Loading FramesTop Loading - Flat BaseBottom Loading FramesSingle Sided TentsDouble Sided Tents Bookstyle Table Tents Four Sided Table TentSix Sided Table TentsThree Sided Table TentEight Sided Table TentsPremium Sign HoldersAcrylic Picture FramesAcrylic Bases/GripsWall Mount Sign HoldersFold Over Wall FramesTop Loading Wall FramesWall Frames with NotchSide Loading Wall FramesSlatwall Sign HoldersStandoff Poster FramesPhoto Booth FramesShelf TalkersBrochure & Literature HoldersCounter Brochure HoldersSingle Pocket HoldersFits up to 4.25" wide Fits up to 6"wideFits up to 8.5"wideFits up to 11"wideMulti-Pocket HoldersEconomy CountertopDeluxe Series HoldersCombination Holders and FramesRotating HoldersJ-StandsWall Mounted HoldersSingle Pocket HoldersEconomy Wall MountFits up to 4.5"wide insertsFits up to 6"wide insertsFits up to 8.5"wide insertsFits up to 11"wide insertsFlat Foldable PocketsMulti-Pocket HoldersSlatwall Brochure HoldersMulti-Pocket HoldersCombination Frames & HoldersSuggestion & Ballot BoxesWithout Sign Header (Riser)With Sign Header (Riser)Open Top BinsWall Mount BoxesWall Poster/Certificate FramesFold Over Wall FramesTop Loading Wall FramesWall Poster Frame with NotchSide Loading Wall FramesSlatwall Sign HoldersBusiness Card DisplaysAccessories & Add-OnsAcrylic ComponentsAdd-On PocketsMounting AccessoriesCeiling HardwareWall HardwareTable HardwareGlass HardwareMagnetic HardwareBallot Box AccessoriesReal Estate & Outdoor
HoldersMerchandise DisplaysMemo Pad / Sticky Note HoldersJ-StandsOpen Top BinsU-RisersCD / DVD HoldersRetail Displays & FixturesEaselsSlatwall DisplaysSlatwall Bins & ShelvesSlatwall Brochure HoldersSlatwall Sign HoldersImprinting ServicesImprinting OptionsAcrylic Care | CleaningAcrylic Flat SheetsMedical IndustryOverstock/Clearance
My Cart
My Account
Buyer's Guide
Buyers Guide
Differences in Material
Thickness of Material
FAQ
Video
My Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Home
/
Privacy Policy
Return to Previous Page
Privacy Policy
We do not sell your information to third parties. Our website server only collects generic website usage information, also called website analytics, or statistics. Analytics data is collected for the purpose of tracking how many visitors come to our website and possibly improving visitors' future visits.  If you would like to correct any of your information or if you have any concerns about the misuse of your personal data please feel free to contact us using the information on this website.  contact us.
The information collected is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of our Web page, not shared with other organizations for commercial purposes. Any non-public personal information that you may provide via our website will be used for the purpose stated on the page where it is collected. (In some cases, and in all cases where required by law or regulation, you will be able to update the information that you provide to us either by sending us an e-mail or, where you have established personal profiles with us, by updating your profile online.
We take your privacy seriously. Our goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this website:
Personal InformationIf you should provide us with your email address or other personal information as part of a subscription or email, we will never provide that email address directly to third-party advertisers. Any information submitted to us is kept completely confidential and will not be shared, sold, traded or rented.
What information do we collect? How do we use it?When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, phone number, mailing address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to process and fulfill your order and to notify you of your order status.
By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post these changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and how we use it.
Contact Us
Displays&Holders2535 W. Via Palma AvenueAnaheim, CA 92801Hours: 7 am - 4 pm PST           (Monday-Friday)
Toll Free:  866.235.1216Phone:     714.527.1179Fax:         714.229.9278
Email: info@displaysandholders.com
Brands We Work With
‹ ›
Customer Service
Have a Question? Contact us by Phone, E-mail or Live Chat!
Buyer's Guide
Learn about what you are buying to make the best purchasing decision!
Made in USA!
All of Our Fabricating, Imprinting, and Shipping Are Performed In-House in Anaheim, CA.
Displays and Holders
| 2535 W. Via Palma Avenue
Anaheim,
CA
92801
| Phone:714-527-1179
